https://www.avertium.com/privacy-policy/

See Avertium CEO’s Message about COVID-19.       +1 (877) 707-7997
Managed Security Services – Extended Detection and Response
Vulnerability Assessment as a Service (VMaaS)
Web + Mobile Application Security Assessment
Digital Forensics and Incident Response (DFIR)
Managed Security Services – Extended Detection and Response
Vulnerability Assessment as a Service (VMaaS)
Web + Mobile Application Security Assessment
Digital Forensics and Incident Response (DFIR)
Managed Security Services – Extended Detection and Response
Vulnerability Assessment as a Service (VMaaS)
Web + Mobile Application Security Assessment
Digital Forensics and Incident Response (DFIR)
Managed Security Services – Extended Detection and Response
Vulnerability Assessment as a Service (VMaaS)
Web + Mobile Application Security Assessment
Digital Forensics and Incident Response (DFIR)
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. This policy describes Avertium’s practices concerning how we handle information we may collect from you via our website, https://www.avertium.com, and other sites we own and operate. Avertium is referred to as “we,” “us” or “our,” and the persons and entities accessing our websites are referred to as “you” and “yours.”1. INFORMATION WE COLLECTLog DataWhen you visit our website, our servers may automatically log the standard data provided by your web browser. It may include your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on each page, and other details.Device DataWe may also collect data about the device you’re using to access our website. This data may include the device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, device settings, and geo-location data. What we collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and software. We recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider to learn what information they make available to us.Personal InformationWe may ask for personal information, such as your:Name; Email; Phone/mobile number; Home/Mailing address; Work address2. LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSINGWe will process your personal information in a lawful manner. We collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so.These legal bases depend on the services you use and how you use them, meaning we collect and use your information only where:it’s necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract (for example, when we provide a service you request from us);it satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your legal right to data protection), such as for research and development, to market and promote our services, and to protect our legal rights and interests;you give us consent to do so for a specific purpose (for example, you might consent to us sending you our newsletter); orwe need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.Where you consent to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time by notifying us in the manner described in this policy (but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place).We don’t keep personal information for longer than is necessary. While we retain this information, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification from third parties. That said, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure and cannot guarantee absolute data security. If necessary, we may retain your personal information for our compliance with a legal obligation or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.3. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATIONWe may collect, hold, use and disclose information for the following purposes and personal information will not be further processed in a manner that is incompatible with these purposes:to enable you to access and use our website, associated applications and associated social media platforms;to contact and communicate with you;for analytics, market research and business development, including to operate and improve our website, associated applications and associated social media platforms;for advertising and marketing, including to send you promotional information about our products and services and information about third parties that we consider may be of interest to you; and to comply with our legal obligations and resolve any disputes that we may have, and;for any other lawful purpose.We may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating this policy, our terms of use, or the law, or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of us, our other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.  We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.4. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD-PARTIESWe may disclose personal information to:Third-party service providers for the purpose of enabling them to provide their services, including (without limitation) IT service providers, data storage, hosting and server providers, ad networks, analytics, error loggers, debt collectors, maintenance or problem-solving providers, marketing or advertising providers, professional advisors and payment systems operators; our employees, contractors and/or related entities; and third parties, including agents or sub-contractors, who assist us in providing information, products, services or direct marketing to you.5. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONThe personal information we collect is stored and processed by us in the United States, and by our partners, affiliates and third-party providers wherever they maintain facilities. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to the disclosure to partners, affiliates and third-party providers in overseas and United States locations.We will ensure that if and to the extent that we transfer personal information from countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) to countries outside the EEA that we will protect such information by any safeguards that we are legally required to follow, for example by using standard data protection clauses approved by the European Commission, or the use of binding corporate rules or other legally accepted means.6. YOUR RIGHTS AND CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONChoice and consent: By providing personal information to us, you consent to us collecting, holding, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. You do not have to provide personal information to us, however, if you do not, it may affect your use of this website or the products and/or services offered on or through it.Information from third parties: If we receive personal information about you from a third party, we will treat it as described in this privacy policy. If you are a third party providing personal information about another person, you represent and warrant that you have such person’s consent to provide the personal information to us.Restrict: You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us using the details below. If you ask us to restrict or limit how we process your personal information, we will let you know how the restriction affects your use of our website or products and services.Access and data portability: You may request details of the personal information that we hold about you. You may request a copy of the personal information we hold about you. Where possible, we will provide this information in CSV format or other easily readable machine format. You may request that we erase the personal information we hold about you at any time. You may also request that we transfer this personal information to another third party.Correction: If you believe that any information we hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please contact us using the details below. We will take reasonable steps to correct any information found to be inaccurate, incomplete, misleading or out of date.Notification of data breaches: We will comply with laws applicable to us in respect of any data breach.Complaints: If you believe that we have breached a relevant data protection law and wish to make a complaint, please contact us using the details below and provide us with full details of the alleged breach. We will promptly investigate your complaint and respond to you, in writing, setting out the outcome of our investigation and the steps we will take to deal with your complaint. You also have the right to contact a regulatory body or data protection authority in relation to your complaint.Unsubscribe: To unsubscribe from our e-mail database or opt-out of communications (including marketing communications), please contact us using the details below or opt-out using the opt-out facilities provided in the communication.7. CALIFORNIA DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURES:Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on the Do Not Track signal, the browser sends a message to websites requesting them not to track the user. For information about Do Not Track, visit www.allaboutdnt.org.We do not honor or respond to Do Not Track signals or requests or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services (collectively, “DNT”).  Because we do not honor or respond to DNT consumers who use DNT mechanisms on or with the website are treated no differently than consumers who do not use DNT.With regard to consumer Personal Identifying Information (“PII”) (i.e., (i) first and last name, (ii) home or other physical address, including  street name and name of a city or town, (iii) e-mail address, (iv) a telephone number, (v) a social security number, or (vi) any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual, or information concerning a user that a web  site or online service collects online from a user and maintains in personally identifiable form in combination with an identifier described in (i)—(v)), PII will be collected by us as described in this privacy policy from users who provide or use DNT with our website in the same manner as we collect such PII from users who do not provide or use DNT with our website.  See the section titled “Cookies and Other Technologies” for additional information.We do not currently track your PII over time and across third-party websites, or allow third parties who may have content on, or links on, the website to collect PII about your online activities when you use our website. However, be aware that such third parties may collect personally identifiable information from you, including if you follow a link on our website to such third party site or content, or if you provide PII to such third parties directly.  We have no control over PII that you provide to third parties, or that third parties collect from you via links to their sites that you access.8. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIESWe use “cookies” to collect information about you and your activity across our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website stores on your computer, and accesses each time you visit, so we can understand how you use our site. This helps us serve you content based on preferences you have specified. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more information.Cookie PolicyWe use cookies to help improve your experience of https://www.avertium.com. This cookie policy is part of Avertium’s privacy policy, and covers the use of cookies between your device and our site. We also provide basic information on third-party services we may use, who may also use cookies as part of their service, though they are not covered by our policy.If you don’t wish to accept cookies from us, you should instruct your browser to refuse cookies from https://www.avertium.com, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired content and services.What is a cookie?A cookie is a small piece of data that a website stores on your device when you visit, typically containing information about the website itself, a unique identifier that allows the site to recognise your web browser when you return, additional data that serves the purpose of the cookie, and the lifespan of the cookie itself.Cookies are used to enable certain features (eg. logging in), to track site usage (eg. analytics), to store your user settings (eg. timezone, notification preferences), and to personalise your content (eg. advertising, language). Cookies set by the website you are visiting are normally referred to as “first-party cookies”, and typically only track your activity on that particular site. Cookies set by other sites and companies (ie. third parties) are called “third-party cookies”, and can be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service.Types of cookies and how we use them:Essential cookiesEssential cookies are crucial to your experience of a website, enabling core features like user logins, account management, shopping carts and payment processing. We do not use this type of cookie on our site.Performance cookiesPerformance cookies are used in the tracking of how you use a website during your visit, without collecting personal information about you. Typically, this information is anonymous and aggregated with information tracked across all site users, to help companies understand visitor usage patterns, identify and diagnose problems or errors their users may encounter, and make better strategic decisions in improving their audience’s overall website experience. These cookies may be set by the website you’re visiting (first-party) or by third-party services. We use performance cookies on our site.Functionality cookiesFunctionality cookies are used in collecting information about your device and any settings you may configure on the website you’re visiting (like language and timezone settings). With this information, websites can provide you with customized, enhanced or optimized content and services. These cookies may be set by the website you’re visiting (first-party) or by third-party service. We use functionality cookies for selected features on our site.Targeting/advertising cookiesTargeting/advertising cookies are used in determining what promotional content is more relevant and appropriate to you and your interests. Websites may use them to deliver targeted advertising or to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. This helps companies improve the effectiveness of their campaigns and the quality of content presented to you. These cookies may be set by the website you’re visiting (first-party) or by third-party services. Targeting/advertising cookies set by third-parties may be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service. We use targeting/advertising cookies on our site.Third-party cookies on our siteWe may employ third-party companies and individuals on our websites—for example, analytics providers and content partners. We grant these third parties access to selected information to perform specific tasks on our behalf. They may also set third-party cookies in order to deliver the services they are providing. Third-party cookies can be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service. As we have no control over third-party cookies, they are not covered by Avertium’s cookie policy.How you can control or opt out of cookiesIf you do not wish to accept cookies from us, you can instruct your browser to refuse cookies from our website. Most browsers are configured to accept cookies by default, but you can update these settings to either refuse cookies altogether, or to notify you when a website is trying to set or update a cookie.If you browse websites from multiple devices, you may need to update your settings on each individual device.Although some cookies can be blocked with little impact on your experience of a website, blocking all cookies may mean you are unable to access certain features and content across the sites you visit. In addition, we may use other technology that is standard to the Internet, such as pixel tags, web beacons and other similar technologies, to track visitors to the website. Those tools may be used by us and by third parties to collect information about you and your internet activity.9. BUSINESS TRANSFERSIf we or our assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, we would include data among the assets transferred to any parties who acquire us. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any parties who acquire us may continue to use your personal information according to this policy.10. LIMITS OF OUR POLICYOur website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.11. CHANGES TO THIS POLICYAt our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect current acceptable practices. We will take reasonable steps to let users know about changes via our website. Your continued use of this site after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information.If we make a significant change to this privacy policy, for example changing a lawful basis on which we process your personal information, we will ask you to re-consent to the amended privacy policy.This policy is effective as of 5 June 2019.
Managed Security Services
Managed LogRhythm
Managed - AT&T Cybersecurity
Managed VMaaS
Managed ZTN Access
Professional Services
Strategic Security Assessment
HITRUST Certification Services
Sign-up for weekly threat reports, tips and security news.
Arizona •  Colorado • Georgia • Pennsylvania • Tennessee • Virginia
Copyright © 2020 Avertium. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
» Document Link
